{
    "subject": "resource/Death_at_a_Funeral_(2010_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Keith_David",
    "human_readable": "Keith David stars in Death at a Funeral (2010 film).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9449992179870605,
            "question": "Who starred in the 2010 film 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9414856433868408,
            "question": "What role did Keith David play in 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8226210474967957,
            "question": "What film did Keith David star in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7143085598945618,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Keith David?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7013840675354004,
            "question": "Name some other films starring Keith David."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.690579354763031,
            "question": "Who are some other actors who appeared in the film 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6341112852096558,
            "question": "In what year was the film 'Death at a Funeral' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5701355338096619,
            "question": "Is there a remake of 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44216734170913696,
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'Death at a Funeral' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3203114867210388,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or prequels to 'Death at a Funeral'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Keith David stars in Death at a Funeral (2010 film).",
            "html": "dbpedia_2946_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the movie 'Death at a Funeral' likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2946_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a remake of 'Death at a Funeral'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2946_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was the film 'Death at a Funeral' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2946_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2946_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Keith David starred in the 2010 film \"Death at a Funeral,\" which directly supports the statement that Keith David stars in the 2010 film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}